[
    {
        "question": "What is 8 ÷ 2?",
        "choice1": "2",
        "choice2": "3",
        "choice3": "4",
        "choice4": "5",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 15 ÷ 3?",
        "choice1": "4",
        "choice2": "5",
        "choice3": "3",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 21 ÷ 7?",
        "choice1": "2",
        "choice2": "3",
        "choice3": "4",
        "choice4": "5",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 12 ÷ 4?",
        "choice1": "3",
        "choice2": "4",
        "choice3": "5",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 30 ÷ 5?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "6",
        "choice3": "4",
        "choice4": "7",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 18 ÷ 2?",
        "choice1": "8",
        "choice2": "17",
        "choice3": "9",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 42 ÷ 6?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "6",
        "choice3": "7",
        "choice4": "8",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 24 ÷ 4?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "7",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 45 ÷ 9?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "6",
        "choice3": "7",
        "choice4": "8",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 27 ÷ 3?",
        "choice1": "7",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "9",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 36 ÷ 6?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "6",
        "choice3": "7",
        "choice4": "8",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 48 ÷ 8?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "6",
        "choice3": "7",
        "choice4": "8",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 63 ÷ 7?",
        "choice1": "8",
        "choice2": "9",
        "choice3": "10",
        "choice4": "11",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 20 ÷ 4?",
        "choice1": "4",
        "choice2": "5",
        "choice3": "6",
        "choice4": "7",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 54 ÷ 9?",
        "choice1": "6",
        "choice2": "7",
        "choice3": "8",
        "choice4": "9",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 90 ÷ 10?",
        "choice1": "8",
        "choice2": "10",
        "choice3": "9",
        "choice4": "11",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 72 ÷ 8?",
        "choice1": "8",
        "choice2": "11",
        "choice3": "10",
        "choice4": "9",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 64 ÷ 4?",
        "choice1": "15",
        "choice2": "16",
        "choice3": "17",
        "choice4": "18",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 81 ÷ 9?",
        "choice1": "7",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "9",
        "choice4": "10",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 99 ÷ 11?",
        "choice1": "9",
        "choice2": "7",
        "choice3": "10",
        "choice4": "11",
        "answer": 1
    }
    
]
